<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>🎲Heroica Wiki</title>
      <link>https://captagonal.github.io/Heroica-Rules</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on 🎲Heroica Wiki</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>Original Rulebook</title>
    <link>https://captagonal.github.io/Heroica-Rules/Original-Rulebook</link>
    <guid>https://captagonal.github.io/Heroica-Rules/Original-Rulebook</guid>
    <description>Playing the game The youngest player goes first. Play then continues clockwise. Moving Heroes On your turn roll the LEGO Dice and move your Hero up to the number of spaces rolled.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 23:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Zombie</title>
    <link>https://captagonal.github.io/Heroica-Rules/Monsters/Zombie</link>
    <guid>https://captagonal.github.io/Heroica-Rules/Monsters/Zombie</guid>
    <description> Lore Zombies are stumbling, ponderous Monsters, aimlessly roaming around the extensive catacomb systems beneath Ilrion. Stupid as they are, Zombies make perfect henchmen for a brilliant mind like the Vampire Lord.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 23:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Vampire Lord</title>
    <link>https://captagonal.github.io/Heroica-Rules/Monsters/Vampire-Lord</link>
    <guid>https://captagonal.github.io/Heroica-Rules/Monsters/Vampire-Lord</guid>
    <description> Lore Deep down under the mountain, hidden in the Ilrion Catacombs, the dreaded Vampire Lord sits on his sumptuous throne. In his underground prison he holds captive the King of Ennon.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 23:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Golems</title>
    <link>https://captagonal.github.io/Heroica-Rules/Monsters/Golems/</link>
    <guid>https://captagonal.github.io/Heroica-Rules/Monsters/Golems/</guid>
    <description>Golems are creatures either resembling rock or literally made of rock. These monsters live deep within the Caverns of Nathuz, where their small numbers are constantly growing.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 23:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Golem Lord</title>
    <link>https://captagonal.github.io/Heroica-Rules/Monsters/Golems/Golem-Lord</link>
    <guid>https://captagonal.github.io/Heroica-Rules/Monsters/Golems/Golem-Lord</guid>
    <description> Lore The Golem Lord was created by ancient magic long ago and gains his power from the living jewel imbedded in his chest. He now stalks the dark Caverns of Nathuz furthering his evil schemes.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 23:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Golem Guardian</title>
    <link>https://captagonal.github.io/Heroica-Rules/Monsters/Golems/Golem-Guardian</link>
    <guid>https://captagonal.github.io/Heroica-Rules/Monsters/Golems/Golem-Guardian</guid>
    <description> Lore The Golem Guardians are summoned minions of the Golem Lord. Reflecting the strength of their master, Golem Guardians are a challenging foe. There are still only a few of them but they are growing in number as the Golem Lord continues to build his army.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 23:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title> Goblins</title>
    <link>https://captagonal.github.io/Heroica-Rules/Monsters/Goblins/</link>
    <guid>https://captagonal.github.io/Heroica-Rules/Monsters/Goblins/</guid>
    <description>The Goblins are the most numerous of all the threatening evil in Ennon, holding about 3 out of and 7 soldiers in the kingdom and surrounding areas to this point ...</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 23:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Goblin Warriors</title>
    <link>https://captagonal.github.io/Heroica-Rules/Monsters/Goblins/Goblin-Warriors</link>
    <guid>https://captagonal.github.io/Heroica-Rules/Monsters/Goblins/Goblin-Warriors</guid>
    <description> Lore Vicious and sneaky, the Goblin Warriors make up the majority of the Goblin army. What they lack in strength they make up in numbers. Wherever you see one there are sure to be more around, waiting to ambush unsuspecting victims.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 23:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Goblin King</title>
    <link>https://captagonal.github.io/Heroica-Rules/Monsters/Goblins/Goblin-King</link>
    <guid>https://captagonal.github.io/Heroica-Rules/Monsters/Goblins/Goblin-King</guid>
    <description> Lore The Goblin King is the ruler of all the goblins. He rose to power by being the meanest and the toughest of them all. Once again released through the rift, the Goblin King now rules over the kingdom of Ennon from Castle Fortaan with an iron fist having crushed anyone who dared to oppose him.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 23:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Goblin Guardians</title>
    <link>https://captagonal.github.io/Heroica-Rules/Monsters/Goblins/Goblin-Guardians</link>
    <guid>https://captagonal.github.io/Heroica-Rules/Monsters/Goblins/Goblin-Guardians</guid>
    <description> Lore The Goblin Guardians are hand-picked by the Goblin King to serve as special troops. Not only used to watch over treasures and secure key positions on the battlefield, they also make up the Goblin King’s personal guard.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 23:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>